A Guide to the Directors' Correspondence of the Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1933-1977 (bulk 1934-1976)
Library of Virginia
- Building: Photos of Drawings, 1965 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 7)
- Building: Planning, 1949-1953 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Building: Plaques - Old Dominion Foundation Fountain, Waddy Fountain and R.E. Lee Camp, 1954-1955 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Building: Plaques - Old Dominion Foundation Fountain; Waddy Fountain; and R.E. Lee Camp, 1954-1955 (OVERSIZE) (Box 81, Folder 12)
- Building: Pratt Installation, 1954-1955 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Building: Pratt Installation, 1954-1955 (OVERSIZE) (Box 81, Folder 13)
- Building: Preliminary Specifications for Additions and Alterations to the Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Building: Prints and Materials, 1962-1969 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Building: Prints and Materials, 1962-1969 (OVERSIZE) (Box 81, Folder 14)
- Building: Projection Room, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Building: Publicity, 1949-1950 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Building: re Contract - Doyle and Russell, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Building: Rest Room, Lobby, undated (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Building: Selection of Architects, 1948 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Building: Service Area, 1959-1960 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Building: Sketches and Drawings, 1949-1951 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Building: Sketches and Drawings, 1949-1951 (OVERSIZE) (Box 82, Folder 1)
- Building: Sound Equipment, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Building: Sound Equipment - Cottrell, 1954-1956 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Building: South Wing - Construction, 1966-1973 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Building: South Wing - Construction, Meetings, 1969-1972 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- Building: South Wing - Dedication 1970, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Building: South Wing - Layout, 1964-1966 (Box 15, Folder 31)
- Building: South Wing - Layout, 1964-1966 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 8)
- Building: South Wing - Layout, 1964-1966 (RESTRICTED OVERSIZE) (Box 87, Folder 13)
- Building: South Wing - Litigation, 1968-1969 (Box 15, Folder 32)
- Building: South Wing - Miscellaneous Additions and Alterations, 1949-1970 (Box 15, Folder 33)
- Building: South Wing - Miscellaneous Additions and Alterations, 1949-1970 (RESTRICTED OVERSIZE) (Box 87, Folder 14)
- Building: South Wing - Opening 1970 Jan 26-29, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 34)
- Building: South Wing - Presentation to State Art Commission, 1965-1970 (Box 15, Folder 35)
- Building: Specifications - Repairs, 1968-1971 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Building: Supplemental Agreement No 2, 279-A, 1955, folder 1 of 2 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Building: Supplemental Agreement No. 2, 279-A, 1955, folder 2 of 2 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Building: Supplemental Agreement No. 2, Contract 279A, 1952-1955 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Building: Tape-Slide System, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Building: Theatre, 1951-1955 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Building: Theatre, 1951-1955 (OVERSIZE) (Box 82, Folder 2)
- Building: Theatre, 1954-1955 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Building: Theatre, 1954-1955 (OVERSIZE) (Box 82, Folder 3)
- Building: Theatre - Color Samples, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Building: Theatre - Equipment, Stands, Ropes, etc., 1955 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Building: Theatre - Photographs and Floor Plans, undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Building: Theatre - Photographs and Floor Plans, undated (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 9)
- Building: Trustee Dinner, 1973 February 15, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Building: USO Auditorium - Theatre for Museum, Col, Anderson, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Building: Waddy Fountain - Flowers, 1955-1956 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Building: Waddy Fountains, 1954-1955 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Building: Wall Covering - Ruskin, 1953-1955 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Building: Wall Coverings - Movable Partitions, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Building and Grounds Committee, 1955-1956 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Building and Grounds Committee: Meeting Minutes, 1957 February 12 (Box 90, Folder 5)
- Building and Grounds Committee: Pending, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Building and Grounds Committee: Pending, 1956 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 10)
- Building Committee: (Local) Statistical Statements, Costs and Funds, 1950-1952 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Building Committee: Architect Plans, 1954-1955, folder 1 of 2 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Building Committee: Architect Plans, 1954-1955, folder 2 of 2 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Building Committee: Architect Plans, 1954-1955 (OVERSIZE) (Box 82, Folder 4)
- Building Committee: Architectural Plans, 1948-1955 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Building Committee: Architectural Plans, 1948-1955 (OVERSIZE) (Box 82, Folder 5)
- Building Committee: Contractors, 1954-1956, folder 1 of 2 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Building Committee: Contractors, 1954-1956, folder 2 of 2 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Building Committee: Contracts, 1954-1956 (OVERSIZE) (Box 82, Folder 6)
- Building Committee: General, 1946-1952 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Building Committee: General, 1949-1950 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Building Committee: General, 1949-1950 (OVERSIZE) (Box 82, Folder 7)
- Building Committee: General, 1949-1950 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 11)
- Building Committee: General, 1949-1950 (RESTRICTED OVERSIZE) (Box 88, Folder 1)
- Building Committee: General, 1951-1954, folder 1 of 2 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Building Committee: General, 1951-1954, folder 2 of 2 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Building Committee: General, 1952-1953 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Building Committee: General, 1953-1954, folder 1 of 2 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Building Committee: General, 1953-1954, folder 2 of 2 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Building Committee: General, 1954-1955, folder 1 of 2 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Building Committee: General, 1954-1955, folder 2 of 2 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Building Committee: General, 1955-1956 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Building Committee: Local Plans, 1935-1951 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Building Committee: Minutes, 1948-1956, folder 1 of 3 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Building Committee: Minutes, 1948-1956, folder 2 of 3 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Building Committee: Minutes, 1948-1956, folder 3 of 3 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Building Program, 1951-1953 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Bulletin: Members, 1946-1956 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Bulletins from Museums of Cities with Population Comparable to Richmond, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Butzner, Mrs. John D., Jr., 1955-1966 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- By-Laws: 1971 Revision, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Bylaws: Amendments, 1941-1956 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Byrd, Harry Flood, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- C: General, 1934-1940 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- C: General, 1954-1958 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- C: General, 1962-1972 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- C: General, 1962-1972 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 12)
- C: General, 1964-1970 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- C: General, 1973-1976 [1] (Box 18, Folder 5)
- C: General, 1973-1976 [2] (Box 18, Folder 6)
- C: General, 1973-1976 [2] (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 13)
- Ca-Cl, 1945-1954 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Ca-Cl, 1945-1954 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 14)
- Ca-Cl, 1959-1965 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Ca-Cl, 1959-1965 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 15)
- Ca-Cl, undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Caligula, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Caligula, 1971 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 16)
- Camp, James L., Jr., 1960-1970 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Canaday, John, 1949-1953 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Capital Outlay, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Carbons, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Carbons, 1956 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 17)
- Carnegie Corporation, 1934-1938 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Carnegie Corporation, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Carnegie Corporation of New York, 1956-1967 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Carnegie Institute, 1935-1944 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Carnegie Institute, 1935-1944 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 18)
- Carnegie Trust Visit 1955 October 5-7, 1955-1956 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Carnegie: Dunfermline Trust, 1955-1961 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Carner, Joseph N., 1955-1957 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Catalogue: 25th Anniversary, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Catalogue: Healy's Sitters, 1950-1955 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Catalogue: Jaquelin-Ambler Portraits, 1939-1952 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Catherwood Foundation, 1955-1956 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Catherwood Foundation Fellowship, 1955-1956 (Box 18, Folder 26)
- Catherwood Foundation Fellowship: Applicants - Arthurs, Pauline M., 1956 (Box 18, Folder 27)
- Catherwood Foundation Fellowship: Applicants - Ayres, Jennie M., 1956 (Box 18, Folder 28)
- Catherwood Foundation Fellowship: Applicants - Bartley, Regina T., 1956 (Box 18, Folder 29)
- Catherwood Foundation Fellowship: Applicants - Bosserman, Joseph N., 1956 (Box 18, Folder 30)
- Catherwood Foundation Fellowship: Applicants - Conn, Norman, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 31)
- Catherwood Foundation Fellowship: Applicants - Davis, R. Lawson, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 32)
- Catherwood Foundation Fellowship: Applicants - Downing, William S., Jr., 1956 (Box 18, Folder 33)
- Catherwood Foundation Fellowship: Applicants - Franklin, Jenny-Lynn, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 34)
- Catherwood Foundation Fellowship: Applicants - Freeman, John Middleton, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 35)
- Catherwood Foundation Fellowship: Applicants - Fuller, Carolyn, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 36)
- Catherwood Foundation Fellowship: Applicants - Fuller, Robert, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 37)
- Catherwood Foundation Fellowship: Applicants - Hanbury, John Paul Conwell, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 38)
- Catherwood Foundation Fellowship: Applicants - Holtzclaw, Ernest L., 1956 (Box 18, Folder 39)
- Catherwood Foundation Fellowship: Applicants - Huff, Caroline, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 40)
- Catherwood Foundation Fellowship: Applicants - Huffman, Ann, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 41)
- Catherwood Foundation Fellowship: Applicants - Jackson, William Ward, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 42)
- Catherwood Foundation Fellowship: Applicants - Langford, Eugene C., 1956 (Box 18, Folder 43)
- Catherwood Foundation Fellowship: Applicants - McGavock, Martha P., 1956 (Box 18, Folder 44)
- Catherwood Foundation Fellowship: Applicants - McGavock, Martha P., 1956 (SLIDES) (Box 89, Folder 10)
- Catherwood Foundation Fellowship: Applicants - Roseburg, Carl, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 45)
- Catherwood Foundation Fellowship: Applicants - Rosenfeld, Louis, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 46)
- Catherwood Foundation Fellowship: Applicants - Thompson, Betty, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 47)
- Catherwood Foundation Fellowship: Applicants - Townsend, Vernon E., 1956 (Box 18, Folder 48)
- Catherwood Foundation Fellowship: Applicants - Twombly, Cy, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 49)
- Catherwood Foundation Fellowship and Virginia Museum of Fine Arts Fellowships: Gaines, William R., 1956-1957 (Box 18, Folder 50)
- Catherwood Foundation Fellowship and Virginia Museum Fellowships: Gaines, William R., 1956-1957 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 19)
- Catherwood Foundation Fellowship: Applications, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 51)
- Catholic Women's Club: 1972 March 21 Luncheon, 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Century Lighting, Inc, 1953-1959 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Chamber Music Society: Sub-Committee Meeting, 1957 November 11 (Box 90, Folder 6)
- Chamber of Commerce - Richmond, 1949-1951 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Chamber of Commerce - Virginia, 1949-1951 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Chapter/Affiliate Correspondence, 1967-1972 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Chapter and Affiliate Winter Conference 1972 February 19, Alexandria, 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Chapter Broadcast Plan, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Chapter Lectures re: New Building, 1965-1966 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Chapter Presidents: Letters to Legislators re New Building, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Chapters and Affiliates, 1974-1976 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Cheatham, Mr. and Mrs. Owen, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Chebry Company, 1950-1953 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Cheek, Leslie, 1936-1942 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Cheek, Leslie, 1960-1970 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Cheek, Leslie, Jr.: Resignation - General, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Cheek, Leslie, Jr.: Resignation - Letters from special friends who did special things, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Cheek, Leslie, Jr.: Resignation - Love letter replies, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Cheek, Leslie, Jr.: Resignation - Museum Directors' Replies, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Cheek-Hudson Interview, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Children's Christmas Party, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Children's Christmas Party 1960 December 18, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Children's Classes, 1948 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Children's Classes, 1948-1949 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Children's Classes, 1949 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Children's Classes, 1950-1954 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- Christison, Mrs., 1954-1968 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- Christison, Mrs.: Correspondence, 1953-1955 (Box 19, Folder 27)
- Christison, Mrs.: Correspondence - Misc., 1949-1952, folder 1 of 2 (Box 19, Folder 28)
- Christison, Mrs.: Correspondence - Misc., 1949-1952, folder 2 of 2 (Box 19, Folder 29)
- Christison, Mrs.: Correspondence, Misc., 1949-1952 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 20)
- Christison, Mrs.: Misc. Correspondence, 1951-1954, folder 1 of 3 (Box 19, Folder 30)
- Christison, Mrs.: Misc. Correspondence, 1951-1954, folder 2 of 3 (Box 19, Folder 31)
- Christison, Mrs.: Misc. Correspondence, 1951-1954, folder 3 of 3 (Box 19, Folder 32)
- Christison, Mrs.: Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1951-1954 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 21)
- Christison, Mrs.: Trips, 1950-1954 (Box 19, Folder 33)
- Christmas, 1954-1956 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Christmas Cards, 1961-1972 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Christmas Greens, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Christmas Story, 1953 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Christmas Story in Art, 1948-1952 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Chronological (Correspondence), 1975 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Chronological (Correspondence), 1975 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 22)
- Chronological File, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Chronological File, 1976 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 23)
- Chrysler Museum, 1973-1976 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Chrysler Museum, Norfolk, 1969-1975 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Chrysler Museum, Norfolk, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Chrysler Museum: Minutes, 1971-1972 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Chrysler Museum: Minutes, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Chrysler Museum: Minutes, 1972-1973 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 24)
- Chrysler Museum: Minutes, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Chrysler Museum: Minutes, 1973-1974 (OVERSIZE) (Box 82, Folder 8)
- Chrysler, Walter, Jr., 1949-1954 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Chrysler, Walter, Jr., 1949-1954 (OVERSIZE) (Box 82, Folder 9)
- Church Silver, 1970 February 2 - March 8, 1968-1970 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Cigar Store Indian Reproductions, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Cigar Store Indians: Reproductions, 1956-1959 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Circularization, 1938 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Circularization, 1939 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Circularization, 1940 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Circularization, 1941 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Circularization, 1942 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Circulars, 1936-1939 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- Civil War Centennial, 1960-1962 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- Civil War Centennial Commission, 1957-1960, folder 1 of 2 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- Civil War Centennial Commission, 1957-1960, folder 2 of 2 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- Civil War Centennial Commission, 1957-1960 (OVERSIZE) (Box 83, Folder 1)
- Civilisation Series, 1970 August 27 - September 17, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 27)
- Civilisation Series, 1970 August 27 - September 17, 1970 (OVERSIZE) (Box 83, Folder 2)
- Civitan Club Dinner 1971 May 18, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 28)
- Cleveland Museum of Art, 1955-1958 (Box 20, Folder 29)
- Cleveland Museum of Art, 1955-1958 (OVERSIZE) (Box 83, Folder 3)
- Cleveland Museum of Art, 1970-1972 (Box 20, Folder 30)
- Clopton, Mrs. Harvie Archer, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 31)
- Club: Poetry Society of Virginia, 1953-1959 (Box 20, Folder 32)
- Co-Cz, 1945-1954 (Box 20, Folder 33)
- Co-Cz, 1945-1954 (OVERSIZE) (Box 83, Folder 4)
- Co-Cz, 1962-1972 (Box 20, Folder 34)
- Cochran, Alexander S., 1949-1953 (Box 20, Folder 35)
- Cocke, C. Francis, 1954-1964 (Box 20, Folder 36)
- Code of Ethics, 1925 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Code of Ethics, 1925-1949 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Coffee Breaks, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Collections, 1975-1976 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Collections, 1975-1976 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 25)
- Collections: Possible Additions, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Collections: Possible Additions, 1950 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 26)
- Collections: Possible Additions, 1951-1953 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 27)
- Collections: Possible Additions, 1953-1954 [1] (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Collections: Possible Additions, 1953-1954 [1] (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 28)
- Collections: Possible Additions, 1953-1954 [2] (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Collections: Possible Additions, 1953-1954 [2] (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 29)
- Collections: Possible Additions, 1953-1954 [3] (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Collections: Possible Additions, 1953-1954 [3] (OVERSIZE) (Box 83, Folder 5)
- Collections: Possible Additions, 1953-1954 [3] (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 30)
- Collections: Possible Additions 1952, 1948-1952 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Collections: Possible Additions 1952, 1948-1952 (OVERSIZE) (Box 83, Folder 6)
- Collections: Possible Additions 1952, 1948-1952 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 31)
- Collections: Possible Additions 1953, 1951-1953 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Collections: Possible Additions, 1954 (3), 1952-1954 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Collections: Possible Additions 1954 (3), 1952-1954 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 32)
- Collector of the Year, 1974-1976 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Collectors Choice, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Collectors Circle, 1960-1967 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Collector's Circle 1972 November 13, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- College Art Association, 1962-1972 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- College Drama Festival, 1963-1964 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Collins, Preston L., 1951-1952 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Colonial Williamsburg, 1946-1956 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Colonial Williamsburg, 1954-1959 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Colonial Williamsburg, 1959-1965 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Colonial Williamsburg, 1966-1973 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Colt, Thomas C., Jr., 1935-1955, folder 1 of 2 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Colt, Thomas C., Jr., 1935-1955, folder 2 of 2 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Colt, Thomas C., Jr., 1935-1955 (OVERSIZE) (Box 83, Folder 7)
- Colt, Thomas C., Jr., 1935-1955 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 33)
- Colt, Thomas C., Jr., 1940-1948 (Box 21, Folder 25)
- Columbia Records, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 26)
- Columbia University: On Fine Arts in Modern Society - A Research Proposal, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 27)
- Columbus Gallery of Fine Arts, 1951-1965 (Box 21, Folder 28)
- Committee Appointment Letters, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 29)
- Committee Appointment Letters, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 30)
- Committee Appointments, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 31)
- Committee Appointments, 1960-1965 (Box 21, Folder 32)
- Committee International Cultural Exchange, 1961-1966 (Box 21, Folder 33)
- Committee: Public Relations and Development, 1954-1960 (Box 21, Folder 34)
- Commonwealth Letterhead, 1970-1972 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Communications Study: "Report to the Virginia Museum of Fine Arts," 1958 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Community College Presidents Meeting 1971 January 21, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Community Colleges, Virginia Dept. of, 1970-1972 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Complaints, 1963-1968 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Complaints, 1973-1976 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Complimentary Cocktails: Junior League Council, Theatre Affiliates, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Complimentary Luncheon 1969 September 8, 1968-1970 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Compliments, 1949-1956 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Compliments, 1956-1957 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Compliments, 1960-1963 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Compliments, 1964-1966 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Compliments, 1966-1968 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Compliments, 1970-1976 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Compliments: Birthday Party, etc., 1961 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Compliments: Birthday Party, etc., 1961 (OVERSIZE) (Box 83, Folder 8)
- Compliments: European Catalogue, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Compliments: Faberge (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Compliments: Faberge Catalogue, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Compliments: Guidebook, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Compliments: Hogarth Catalogue, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Compliments: Painting in England Catalogues, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Compliments: Painting in England Exhibition, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Compliments: Shakespeare Catalogue, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 23)
- Composing for Dr. Higgins, 1959-1960 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Composing for Mr. Pollard, 1959-1960 (Box 22, Folder 25)
- Confederacy, The: Re-performance of, 1954-1955 (Box 22, Folder 26)
- Confederate Memorial Chapel, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 27)
- Confederate Memorial Chapel, 1966 (OVERSIZE) (Box 83, Folder 9)
- Confederate Women, Home For, 1951-1955 (Box 22, Folder 28)
- Confederation Workshop, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 29)
- Congratulations and Replies: James M. Brown, 1969-1970 (Box 22, Folder 30)
- Congreve (nee Glascow), undated (Box 22, Folder 31)
- Congreve, Mrs. Ambrose, 1966-1971 (Box 22, Folder 32)
- Connor, Carl Y., 1939-1940 (Box 22, Folder 33)
- Conservation, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 34)
- Constable, W.G., 1950-1964 (Box 22, Folder 35)
- Constable, W.G., 1950-1954 (OVERSIZE) (Box 83, Folder 10)
- Contracts - Capitol Superintendent of Buildings and Grounds, 1952-1955 (Box 22, Folder 36)
- Conversations in the Library, 1956-1957 (Box 22, Folder 37)
- Corcoran Gallery, 1951-1960 (Box 22, Folder 38)
- Cornell, Katherine, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 39)
- Corning Glass Center, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 40)
- Corning Glass Center / Museum, 1969-1976 (Box 22, Folder 41)
- Corporate Giving, 1953-1957 (Box 22, Folder 42)
- Corporate Patrons, 1969-1970 (Box 22, Folder 43)
- Corporate Patrons (State and Richmond), 1968-1969 (Box 22, Folder 44)
- Corporate Patrons: "Fete Aux Galeries," 1971-1972 (Box 22, Folder 45)
- Corporate Patrons: "Fete Aux Galeries", 1971-1972 (OVERSIZE) (Box 83, Folder 11)
- Correspondence, 1955-1956, folder 1 of 2 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1955-1956, folder 2 of 2 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1955-1956 (OVERSIZE) (Box 83, Folder 12)
- Correspondence, 1955-1957, folder 1 of 2 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1955-1957, folder 2 of 2 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1955-1957 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 34)
- Correspondence, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1964 (OVERSIZE) (Box 83, Folder 13)
- Correspondence and notes, undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1952-1956, folder 1 of 2 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1952-1956, folder 2 of 2 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1952-1956 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 35)
- Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1956-1957 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1956-1957 (OVERSIZE) (Box 83, Folder 14)
- Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1956-1957 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 36)
- Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1957-1958 (OVERSIZE) (Box 83, Folder 15)
- Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1958 (OVERSIZE) (Box 83, Folder 16)
- Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1958-1969 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1958-1969 (OVERSIZE) (Box 83, Folder 17)
- Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1958-1969 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 37)
- Correspondence: Velz, 1955-1956 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Correspondence: Velz, 1955-1956 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 38)
- Council, 1955-1965 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Council, 1955-1956 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 39)
- Council: Correspondence, 1965-1970 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Council: Correspondence, 1965-1970 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 40)
- Council: The Ball, 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Council of the Museum, 1954-1956 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Council of the Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1969-1972 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Council of the Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1969-1972 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 41)
- Council of the Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Council of the Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1975-1976 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Craftsmen-in Residence, 1962-1965 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Crandall, Robert, 1955-1956 (Box 24, Folder 2)